I braided it the other day, too.
You just let her do what she wants, huh.
Oh, wow!
That's so cute, Miyamura-kun!
I love your hair like that!
Me, too! You should keep it that way!
Oh, Hori-san did it for you? It's adorable!
Man, your face is so tiny and cute, too!
Oh, there's the bell.
See you tomorrow!
--Ow!
--Hori! It's not his fault!
C'mon, let's go!
Hey...
"Horimiya"
Hey, can I have my bag?
Are you mad at me?
Is it because of those girls?
Well, yeah, duh!
They treated you like you were invisible before,
but as soon as you cut your hair,
oh, now they see you!
And they keep putting their paws
all over you right in front of me!
Not really.
You sure?
Miyamura?
It is you.
You should probably stop, dude.
He's all gloomy and depressing.
Whoa, I totally couldn't tell.
Good eye, Tanihara.
Dude, you're such an ass.
So what? You been doing okay?
--Yeah.
--Damn, dude, you got tall.
And holy shit, your piercings.
--Yeah.
--Damn, dude, you got tall.
And holy shit, your piercings.
Glad you guys are doing okay, too, Tanihara.
Ugh, when you say my name,
it totally skeeves me out.
What, did you finally grow
a pair in high school? Dumbass.
And what the hell? You having
some weak-ass chick carry your bag?
Cut it out, Tanihara.
She might be his girlfriend.
Damn, you really scored, Miyamura. Nice job.
C'mon, say something.
Are you done?
Oh, hey, are you his girlfriend?
Do you know what he was like in middle school?
He was so emo and always by himself!
Talk about pathe--
Hey.
I'm asking if you guys are done talking.
Are you?
Huh?
If you are, then piss off, assholes.
I mean, I was already in a crappy mood,
but then they started treating you like that.
How was I supposed to hold back?
Yeah.
Seriously, I can't believe
they were so mean to you!
"It's Hard, but Not Impossible"
Yeah.
A small fry and a drink. Is that all?
Damn, Tanihara...
Did you start taking
karate classes or something?
I just ran into Miyamura.
Miyamura?
Didn't you use to tease
him back in middle school?
"Bunnies"
Whatever.
Y'know, there was this chick with him.
I think she was his girlfriend.
Do you know her, Shindo?
Miyamura's girlfriend? Oh, you mean Hori-san.
So her name's Hori-san.
You should probably stop
teasing him like you did back then.
Miyamura's really leveled up his DEF stats.
What, is his girlfriend his summon or something?
He says he doesn't care about him,
but he keeps bothering him.
He just can't get him out of his head.
Does it hurt?
Huh? What're you talking about?
Never mind.
Thanks, Hori-san.
What's going on? Out with it!
I have someone who'll get mad on my behalf.
She's right here with me.
U-Use your open hand.
Just a little slap!
No.
Why not? You did it before,
just do it again, like bam!
I said, no way!
C'mon, please!
Just one more!
That is the least punchable face ever.
C'mon, she's begging you, Miyamura!
Where the hell did you come from, Shindo?!
Over there.
I was just gonna stalk you from afar,
but you were being so mean to
Hori-san that I just couldn't just watch!
What kind of man are you?!
You were stalking me?
Stay out of this.
You have no idea what's going on.
I mean, it's probably something sexual, right?
Not at all.
Aww, what, do you not love me anymore?
Th-That's not it!
Aww, poor Hori-san!
Quiet, you!
Hey, I can help you instead!
Whatever you want, I'm here.
Or am I the wrong man for the job?
Yep. It's gotta be Miyamura.
So it is something sexual!
Do you even have a brain in there, dude?!
Look, we're leaving! C'mon, Hori-san.
Hori-san?
Louder.
Oh my God!
Move your ass, Kyoko!
Later, Shindo! And this
isn't anything sexual, got it?!
G-Got it.
Ooh, can we go by the
convenience store, Miyamura?
Sure, you dumb bitch!
What the actual hell?
Tanihara.
I'm thirsty. Buy me a drink.
Buy your own damn drink!
Whoa, who put a stick up your ass?
Shut up.
Stop loitering in the parking lot, morons.
The hell's your problem, bitch?!
It's his summon!
How about you take your bitch ass and--
Don't talk to her like that, you moron!
Why're you yelling at me?!
We're not loitering! We're picking up trash!
Yeah, yeah! We're Recycling Buddies!
Oh, is that it? Good work, guys.
That was a close one.
Dude, if you'd pissed her off,
she would've bashed our skulls in!
What, like some monster?
Hey, isn't that Miyamura?
Ugh. Next time I see that guy--
"Got snacks!"
"WHAP"
"You sure took your time, bitch!"
"I'm sorry. I'm so sorry."
"Get a move on, moron!"
"Us < Kyoko Hori < Miyamura"
He's a monster, too!
Holy shit.
What the hell happened to you guys?
I don't mean to kinkshame, but...
Is she right in the head?
Hori-san, look...
It's fine. Whatever you want.
I'm just going to stop thinking about it.
Miyamura sure has changed, like damn.
A high school transformation?
That's still some transformation.
He barely talked back to us in middle school,
and now he's hitting girls?
I'm leaving.
Wait, you're leaving?
Dammit.
I'm back!
I'm heading out!
Already?
Be back by dinner!
You're still here, Kyosuke?
I can't believe I have to say this,
but this is my house, too.
Oh, Kyosuke-san.
Could I ask you for your advice?
Hell yeah, I'm in!
Wait, what? That's suspicious.
Shut it, it's time for a man-to-man!
So, what's up? You good?
Why're we in the bathroom?
I had a question for you about Hori-san.
Damn, she preggers again?
What do you mean, again?!
No, no, just... she really likes it
when I get mad and yell at her.
The hell? Is that her kink or something?
"Deflates"
That's what I thought, too.
Maybe it's just 'cause it's the exact
opposite of how you normally act?
The exact opposite?
Like if you got all dressed up
to go to the office?
"Smart!"
Like if you got all dressed up
to go to the office?
"Smart!"
Ouch, but yeah.
Think of it like taming a fierce golem!
That makes sense.
C'mon, get out of there.
How am I supposed to bathe?
Kyoko! C'mere and sit down!
No thanks.
But look how sad and worried Miyamura-kun is!
You're such a pain.
Miyamura-kun's trying so hard
to live up to your expectations!
What?! Where's this coming from?!
I don't need you to lecture me here!
Stop blabbing about stupid crap
and help out with the chores for once!
She has a point.
Ow, my feelings!
Hey, I made curry the other day! That counts!
No, it doesn't!
All you did was microwave it!
But you said it was yummy!
Yeah, because they make
the prepackaged stuff yummy!
Hey! Sota even got seconds!
Why is it perfectly warm?!
Miyamura-kun's dripping wet!
--Get your clothes off, quick!
--Wait, hold on!
Don't strip in front of me, moron!
So I went to karaoke with Shu the other day.
Sing in English? No way, man! It's way too hard.
All he ever sings are enka songs and rap.
He sure does listen to everything, huh.
I know he listens to
Western pop, too, but damn...
Hey, Mizouchi.
Damn, straight ignored.
Probably 'cause I'm here.
Huh?
Apparently he has a crush on Hori-san.
Damn, how many guys want to be with her now?
"rrrrrumble..."
There's one thing I know
about crushing on Hori-san...
"rrrrrumble..."
Don't fall for her unless you really mean it.
Speaking of Hori, where's she at?
The student council room, I think.
Oh, I don't have my phone.
Did you leave it in the science lab?
I'll go look.
"Science Lab"
Did you forget something, too, Mizouchi-kun?
Have you seen my phone?
No.
Okay.
Why would it be in there?
Well, nobody else has
had class in here since we did,
so it's gotta still be in here somewhere.
What's your number?
Huh?
I'll call it.
Umm, 090...
Found it.
It was in your pocket the whole time?
Thanks! You're a lifesaver--
Wait, why's the screen all black?
How did you break it two seconds later?!
Why the hell is she with you?!
No, I didn't mean...
Hey, Mizouchi-kun...
If you had to... could you punch Hori-san?
What?! Punch her?! Like, if were fighting?
Yeah, I suppose, kinda.
Oh. I could never hit Hori!
Really?
Then you could never be with her.
Hey, Miyamura! Did you find your phone?
Huh? Why?
Toru told me you're always
leaving it all over the place.
You'd better be more careful with your--
Shut the hell up, bitch! Stay quiet for once!
Move!
--Hori!
--Leave her alone, Mizouchi-kun.
Oh... uh, okay.
Miyamura...
I thought you were the kind of guy
who could never stand up for himself.
I thought you were some loser.
But guess it's easy for you to be
confident around your girlfriend, huh?
Yeah, super easy.
Whoa, why are your eyes all red?!
Were you rubbing them or something?!
Miyamura! Go away, there's not enough room!
Go where?
Outside, jeez! Where are we, anyway?!
Outside.
Huh?
This is outside. The only free space there is.
What the hell?! This locker
or whatever isn't "outside" at all!
This is what it's like "outside."
You've always been on the "inside,"
so you don't know how it feels.
Inside, outside, what the hell are you on about?
You're the one who brought it up.
I think this is the first time
we've ever talked like this.
Do you not like tight spaces?
I hate them.
Huh. So do I.
Do you like being on the inside?
It's better than this.
Even if there's nobody on the inside?
If all the people on the inside
with you came outside,
then you'd be all alone in there.
Yeah...
You don't care if you're inside or outside.
You just care that people are there with you.
People who are on your side.
That's it.
I just...
"Bunnies"
Huh? Miyamura's number?
Yeah, I have it, but why do you want it?
Doesn't matter, just tell me.
Okay, just hold on.
Everyone knew the rabbits liked
Miyamura better than anyone.
Huh? Why're we talking about rabbits?
Shut up. Just tell me his number.
Ugh, he's ignoring me.
Izumi! Could you go take the sign in?
Got it.
You guys closed already?
Sorry, we'll be closed tomorrow, too,
but we'll be open the day after...
If you turn the corner and go down for a bit,
you'll find another cake shop.
You'll find a much bigger bakery
that's probably still open now.
I want something from here.
Oh, uh, you sure?
It's fine, I'll come back
the day after tomorrow.
I hear your cheesecake's good.
It is.
Cool. See you in two days, then.
Oh, our fruit tart's good!
It's good, too.
Then I'll get that one, too.
Two of each.
Two of each, got it.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Oh, I tried calling you!
You did?
Sorry, my phone's busted.
I'm gonna go get it fixed tomorrow.
Oh. Okay.
I totally thought he was ignoring me...
I was the one ignoring him all this time.
It was me.
Did it stress you out?
Huh?
No, never mind! I'm heading out.
Tanihara-kun?
Thanks for coming.
I forgot to feed them.
Even though I was supposed to.
By end of summer break, they were all dead.
I was the one who told
everyone it was your fault.
It was me!
Okay.
Miyamura, you know, I'm...
I'm...
I'm sorry.
What if I'd been able to tell him back then?
It hurts my heart to think about it.
Okay, last one.
Thanks for helping out.
Yearbooks!
Oh, that's from middle school.
What'd she look like back then?
Peek and you're a dead man.
They're so annoying.
They're big, and in the way, but you don't
actually wanna throw them away...
Did you throw yours away already, Miyamura?
"Yearbook"
I wanted to...
But they're so huge and heavy,
I didn't know what to do with them,
so I just ended up keeping them.
Now, though, they're actually
pretty important to me.
Back then, Miyamura must've
wanted to throw it all away.
I don't know what he was
like back in middle school,
but I get the feeling that he hated
everything and was just drifting along.
That that's what life was like for him.
But now, he can look back and feel glad
that he didn't throw it all away.
Wonder what Katagiri's
yearbook is going to look like.
Guess we'll find out when we get it.
They took the pictures
for it back in April, right?
I hope they got a picture
of me with Mizouchi-kun.
Wait, why Mizouchi?
We've kinda gotten close lately.
Really?
He helped me find my phone.
He was kind of mean
to me before, but it's all good.
Does he get off on that?
I think I might get along
with Tanihara-kun, too.
Wow.
It might be really hard,
but I don't think there's a person in the world
you can't eventually be friends with.
"Next Time: Until the Snow Melts"